What industry did you pursue a career in? What
do you guys do for a living right now?
I pursued a career in e-commerce.
As an e-commerce business owner, what has been the most
amount of money that you've ever made in a single year?
Fifteen and a half million.
A hundred million.
Like a hundred and eighty thousand.
What's the best financial advice that
you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
If you're going to work, like everyone's going to have to work,
you might as well get paid really well while you do it.
How did you become a millionaire?
Trapping Turner Rappin.
Yes, sir.
We're in Miami, Florida at the Fashion District going all around asking
luxury shoppers what they do for a living and how they became wealthy.
What industry did you pursue a career in? What
do you guys do for a living right now?
I own a medical device company, like a
distributorship for a medical device company from Europe.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
My company's still a baby, so we're still in
the, you know, three, four million at the moment.
That's incredible.
Yeah, it's brand new though.
As an entrepreneur, if you were to go
back to when you first started that business,
what's the number one thing
you wish you would have known?
What's your best advice to any
entrepreneur who's starting a business in 2023?
Hire slow and fire fast.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
I am a physician and I own med spas.
That's amazing.
I inject, yeah. Botox, fillers,
all that kind of fun stuff.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Fifteen and a half million. Gross.
Net would have been half of that.
What was the best financial advice
that you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
So maybe you had a mentor or someone
that told you a lesson about money that is,
stuck with you for your entire life.
What's the best financial advice you tell
the younger generation that someone told you?
Someone once told me when I
was younger, you're going to work,
like everyone's going to have to work.
You might as well get paid
really well while you do it.
And so I look for something that I
could be passionate about, that I could enjoy,
but also pay really well.
So find something you love that also pays well.
In 60 seconds, what is the blueprint
to becoming a millionaire in today's world?
So let's say someone's 25, 26.
You're having a conversation with them.
They want to become serious about becoming financially free.
What was the blueprint?
What you took to create a
seven figure company and become financially free?
It's really about being willing to keep going.
If you get no for an answer, you know,
take a risk too.
Like you got to be willing
to put it on the line, man.
Like I started my business while I was
a resident and I started with my personal
credit cards and I kept getting
an additional credit card because I couldn't
pay off the balance in time. So
it's like transfer balances for like two years.
The day I finally paid off all of
my personal credit cards and cut them all up
was amazing. So like you
got to be willing to hustle.
You got to be willing to take a risk.
And so if you have like the vision
and opportunity, just kind of go for it, man.
Just got to do it.
You guys are awesome. Thank you
guys so much for your time.
Absolutely.
I want to see this channel.
Absolutely. Yeah, for sure.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
I'll call you, man. Yeah, we got
a channel called the School of Hard Knocks.
We've done interviews with like
Mark Heumann, the president of Nike.
I love your videos.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
For those that don't know.
I pursued a career in e-commerce.
So, yeah, starting online businesses,
just mainly everything like online selling
products is where is where I
made the majority of my money.
But now just kind of like
more into real estate, so like more like hard assets.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
In a year, last year we did eight point
seven million dollars in profit and
around 17, 18 million dollars in revenue.
What does it take to get
from a seven to eight figure business?
You know, someone maybe they're they're
doing a million dollars a year, but
they really want to get to 10 million.
Like what was the biggest thing that you
changed in your business to get
you from seven to eight figures?
Yeah, so I always tell people, you know,
you can make it like a million dollars by
yourself, like going from zero to a million.
You can do that by yourself.
But going
from like one million to 10
million, now you need a team.
So the biggest thing was
how can I duplicate myself enough
so that I can be kind
of like outside of the picture
but still generating money.
So I just had to like
copy myself like three, four times
and have people who saw my vision
and people who are smarter than me.
At the end of the
day, I was a college dropout,
but my CFO went to
Stanford, my CFO went to Yale.
So it's just like doing people
who can do what you can do,
but better so that you can
do what only you can do,
which is sit back, come up with the ideas
on how to make more millions
or how to expand and grow your business.
In 60 seconds, what is the blueprint
to becoming a millionaire in today's world?
So let's say someone's 25,
26, they're in their second job.
They wanna get serious about becoming financially free.
They're starting, they wanna drop it,
they wanna go all in.
How can someone become a millionaire today?
Learn a skill.
Learn a skill and don't put
a time limit on that skill.
Don't say, okay, I wanna do this in six months.
Don't say, I wanna do this in three months.
Learn a skill, master that skill to the T
so that you know everything inside of it.
And fail.
Fail a couple times so that
you know exactly what not to do.
And the more times you
fail, the more times you learn.
A lot of people view failures as something that's bad.
It's really good,
because now you know exactly what not to do.
So in today's generation,
if you wanna make a lot of money,
you have to learn a
skill that the economy deems valuable.
You can't just say, okay, I wanna do this.
What does the economy deem valuable?
There's not a lot of people
who know how to make websites.
So learn how to make a website.
That's a great skill.
It's all skill-based.
School teaches you how to become an employee.
Learn how to become a boss.
Wow, my man.
You're taking your time, bro.
I appreciate that, man.
It was so cool to run into you.
Seriously, man.
That's awesome.
Hey, it's crazy, man.
We're doing an interview.
I've seen that guy's content on TikTok
for the last three years.
That guy's really about his business, bro.
He's about millions.
So hey, crush that shit.
Let's get on to the next one.
Can we get you real quick?
Hold on a second.
We got you?
Let me get fresh to death for this.
Let me get you, brother.
I gotta call you back.
I'm being interviewed by a bunch of fucking Austin hunks.
All right?
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Well, as you can see,
this barbershop has done well for me
because it allows me to travel anywhere in the world
and I always have employment.
So you own this barbershop right here?
I don't have to own it to work here,
but I still do good.
That's amazing.
Yes, it is.
What's the best financial advice
that you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
So maybe you had a mentor or someone tell you
a piece of financial advice
that always stuck with you throughout your life.
What's your best financial advice
to the younger generation?
The best financial advice I would give a younger generation?
Make your money make money for you, plain and simple.
It's not about making money.
You could work 40, 50, 60 hours a week.
You could, like I said,
have a regular nine to five, have an employer.
But the minute that money runs out,
the minute your employer, you know,
fires you or whatnot,
then you're back to square
one trying to scramble for money.
However, if that money is working for you,
even when you're sleeping, vacationing,
or engaging in other curricular activities,
get them paid.
When you're in school, kids kind of mock those
that are focused on their studies
or actually educating themselves
rather than engaging in the partying
and hanging out and the drugs.
However, you know, when you come to see those
that were partying and like the life of everything
or the jocks, I don't want to say all jocks,
they're usually the ones asking those kids
to stay at home studying and mastering the crafts
for jobs in their mid-20s.
So the kids mastering the crafts at the early ages
are the ones that live a carefree life
at the later ages in life.
Man, thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate you, man.
You crushed that.
School of Hard Knocks?
School of Hard Knocks.
What, on YouTube?
Instagram, everywhere.
School of Hard Knocks.
I love this shit.
This shit is hilarious.
No, it's a fact.
Listen, that's why I cut hair,
because I like talking to kids like y'all.
I'm from Queens.
In 60 seconds, how can someone become a millionaire
in today's world?
What's the secret to becoming wealthy?
How did you become a millionaire?
Working very hard.
Yeah.
And music.
Absolutely.
Rapping.
I'm trapping to rapping.
Trapping, turning to rapping.
Yes, sir.
And what advice would you tell your younger self?
You're going back in time.
You're starting from zero.
What would you tell your younger self?
Do whatever the fuck you want.
Yes, sir.
Don't take no for an answer from nobody.
Absolutely.
What's your best advice to any entrepreneur
starting a business?
It's not easy.
It's competitive.
How are you able to stand out, man?
Doing different shit.
Yeah.
I really appreciate your time, man.
That means so much to us, man.
World is Yours 2, one of
my favorite albums of all time.
What just happened?
Bro, we just interviewed Rich
the Kid at the stoplight, bro.
That joint's crazy, bro.
It's crazy because he's got a couple of songs.
I'll go back and play out of nowhere, bro.
Crazy, man.
Miami, you never know who you're going
to come in contact with, bro.
That's crazy, dude.
I am.
That was amazing, bro.
That's incredible.
World is Yours 2, World is Yours 1, great albums
when I was coming out of high school, bro.
I'm so excited we got that interview.
That was lit.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
I'm in tech.
I had an e-commerce business,
and I invested in tech companies.
What'd you sell?
Cosmetics.
As an e-commerce business owner, what
has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Depends.
We were a big company.
So in Brazil, we're larger than Sephora online.
Did like around $100 million.
$200 million a year.
What is the best financial advice
that you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
So like, if there's one money lesson
that a mentor ever taught you, what's
the best financial advice that you've ever received?
Yeah, so a penny saved is a penny earned.
When you raise money, like with VCs and everything,
don't spend it all.
Just hold on to your cash.
Think before you act.
And then keep measuring, because you can't take money
for granted, you know?
So you've got to create value out of it,
not just go spending it like they
think it's never.
And that's a very, very important thing.
And that's why I'm here.
I'm here to tell you a story.
I'm here to tell you a more in-depth story.
Sometimes you run out of money.
So you heard it from him.
His e-commerce business is doing bigger than Sephora
for cosmetics in South America.
That's crazy.
Nine-figure e-commerce entrepreneur
out here in Miami, Florida.
Let's go talk to some more beasts out here.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Hospitality.
I'm with 11 USA Group.
We own and operate 11 Miami, Gold Rush Cabaret,
and Giselle Rooftop.
You work in the hospitality.
What is your best networking advice
if you want to become a real estate developer
but you're dead broke?
Attend these real estate conventions.
Be in the rooms with the people that you want
to be when you're older.
Network with as many people as you can
and just get yourself in the room.
Treat everybody with equal amount of respect.
I'm the type of guy
that when I get to work,
I shake the bathroom attendant's hand
and I shake the owner's hand
and I treat them the same.
And I think that's been something that's helped me
succeed in this industry is just treating everybody
with the equal amount of respect.
Pretty cool.
I had a few interviews with one of the guys
that runs the scene down there
at the 11 nightclub in Miami.
It is the largest nightclub in Miami,
one of the biggest nightclubs in the world,
giving some game on how he was able to break
in the nightclub industry and find success.
Question for you guys.
My brother and my friend and I,
we started a channel at
the University of Texas at Austin
that we grew to 1.5 million followers.
We go all over the country.
We're based in Austin, Texas.
Just ask people a few quick questions on their advice
to the younger generation of kids coming out of school
and starting out in the real world.
Wanted to know if we could
ask you guys a few questions
for our channel on how you guys became successful.
Oh, OK.
Does that be cool?
Yeah, that's all right.
Awesome.
Y'all talking to somebody for real.
Y'all know that, right?
Yeah.
I believe it.
Y'all really talking to somebody for real.
Look.
Look, look, look, look.
We going to pop out with y'all.
Yes, sir.
If y'all want, y'all can come
to the Gucci store with me, man.
Look.
I went to Simeon, man.
I graduated in the 06, man.
I'm from Chicago, born and raised.
I lost my twin brother, man.
Let me tell you something.
I had to become an entrepreneur at an early age.
I make clothes.
I do music, man.
I do brand consulting.
I do major and independent consulting.
So it's a lot of people
that want to do what I do.
And at ease, I do
what I do because I love
to do what I just love to do.
But people got to pay me to
do what they want me to do
because I love to do what I do.
What has been the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
Most amount of money I
made in a real single year,
legitly on camera, like $180,000.
What is the best financial advice
that you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
So like if there's one
thing that a mentor or someone
in your life taught you about
money that always stuck with you,
what's the best money lesson that you would tell
the younger generation today?
Know Gaga.
So meaning my brand is called No Talking.
So that's the parent phase of Know Gaga.
So it's Know Gaga, Know Blah Blah, Know Talk.
So basically don't talk about what you're going to do
and just do it.
Put your actions where your mouth is.
Let the money come to you.
Don't chase it.
What's for you is going to be for you.
And that's success.
So anybody that's feeling less confident than success,
it's just not meant for you.
That's amazing, bro.
You crushed that, man.
Thank you so much, bro.
I appreciate you.
To wrap on today's video,
be sure to leave a like
and subscribe for tons of amazing content
coming soon.
And click here to watch this one
around Houston asking millionaires
how they became successful.